{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Structural Engineers","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40032/":{"taskOID":40032,"originalTaskOID":40032,"setID":356,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":5537,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of project is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4163,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New home","answerDisplayText":"New home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":678,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Addition not attached to home","answerDisplayText":"Addition not attached to home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":676,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Addition attached to home","answerDisplayText":"Addition attached to home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5121,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Remodel","answerDisplayText":"Remodel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6156,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Structural repair on existing structure","answerDisplayText":"Structural repair on existing structure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5335,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Retaining wall","answerDisplayText":"Retaining wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5738,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Engineer","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of engineer do you need?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6153,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Structural","answerDisplayText":"Structural","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3785,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Mechanical","answerDisplayText":"Mechanical","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1401,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Civil","answerDisplayText":"Civil","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2901,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"HVAC","answerDisplayText":"HVAC","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1497,"questionDisplayText":"Need for Engineer","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Why do you need an engineer? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5758,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Sizing of interior supports","answerDisplayText":"Sizing of interior supports","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1567,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Concrete foundation specifications","answerDisplayText":"Concrete foundation specifications","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5411,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Roof specifications","answerDisplayText":"Roof specifications","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5757,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Sizing deck supports","answerDisplayText":"Sizing deck supports","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6032,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Stamped drawings for building department approval","answerDisplayText":"Stamped drawings for building department approval","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1903,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Determine load bearing walls","answerDisplayText":"Determine load bearing walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1881,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Design appropriate structural repair(s)","answerDisplayText":"Design appropriate structural repair(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3235,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Inspect repairs during and after work","answerDisplayText":"Inspect repairs during and after work","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6301,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Test structures to withstand natural forces, including earthquakes, water, wind, and snow","answerDisplayText":"Test structures to withstand natural forces, including earthquakes, water, wind, and snow","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":359,"questionDisplayText":"Architectural drawings","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Are there architectural drawings for your project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1498,"questionDisplayText":"Wall Construction Type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of wall construction are you using?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7069,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wood frame","answerDisplayText":"Wood frame","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3811,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Metal frame","answerDisplayText":"Metal frame","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3757,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Masonry","answerDisplayText":"Masonry","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":18055,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Framing not involved in project","answerDisplayText":"Framing not involved in project","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":5537,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Project","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of project is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":4163,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New home","answerDisplayText":"New home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":678,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Addition not attached to home","answerDisplayText":"Addition not attached to home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":676,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Addition attached to home","answerDisplayText":"Addition attached to home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5121,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Remodel","answerDisplayText":"Remodel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6156,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Structural repair on existing structure","answerDisplayText":"Structural repair on existing structure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5335,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Retaining wall","answerDisplayText":"Retaining wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":4163,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"New home","answerDisplayText":"New home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":678,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Addition not attached to home","answerDisplayText":"Addition not attached to home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":676,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Addition attached to home","answerDisplayText":"Addition attached to home","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5121,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Remodel","answerDisplayText":"Remodel","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6156,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Structural repair on existing structure","answerDisplayText":"Structural repair on existing structure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5335,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Retaining wall","answerDisplayText":"Retaining wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":5738,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Engineer","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of engineer do you need?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6153,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Structural","answerDisplayText":"Structural","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3785,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Mechanical","answerDisplayText":"Mechanical","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1401,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Civil","answerDisplayText":"Civil","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2901,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"HVAC","answerDisplayText":"HVAC","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6153,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Structural","answerDisplayText":"Structural","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3785,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Mechanical","answerDisplayText":"Mechanical","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1401,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Civil","answerDisplayText":"Civil","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2901,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"HVAC","answerDisplayText":"HVAC","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1497,"questionDisplayText":"Need for Engineer","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Why do you need an engineer? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5758,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Sizing of interior supports","answerDisplayText":"Sizing of interior supports","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1567,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Concrete foundation specifications","answerDisplayText":"Concrete foundation specifications","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5411,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Roof specifications","answerDisplayText":"Roof specifications","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5757,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Sizing deck supports","answerDisplayText":"Sizing deck supports","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6032,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Stamped drawings for building department approval","answerDisplayText":"Stamped drawings for building department approval","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1903,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Determine load bearing walls","answerDisplayText":"Determine load bearing walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1881,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Design appropriate structural repair(s)","answerDisplayText":"Design appropriate structural repair(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3235,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Inspect repairs during and after work","answerDisplayText":"Inspect repairs during and after work","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6301,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Test structures to withstand natural forces, including earthquakes, water, wind, and snow","answerDisplayText":"Test structures to withstand natural forces, including earthquakes, water, wind, and snow","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5758,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Sizing of interior supports","answerDisplayText":"Sizing of interior supports","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1567,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Concrete foundation specifications","answerDisplayText":"Concrete foundation specifications","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5411,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Roof specifications","answerDisplayText":"Roof specifications","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5757,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Sizing deck supports","answerDisplayText":"Sizing deck supports","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6032,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Stamped drawings for building department approval","answerDisplayText":"Stamped drawings for building department approval","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1903,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Determine load bearing walls","answerDisplayText":"Determine load bearing walls","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1881,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Design appropriate structural repair(s)","answerDisplayText":"Design appropriate structural repair(s)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3235,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Inspect repairs during and after work","answerDisplayText":"Inspect repairs during and after work","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6301,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Test structures to withstand natural forces, including earthquakes, water, wind, and snow","answerDisplayText":"Test structures to withstand natural forces, including earthquakes, water, wind, and snow","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":359,"questionDisplayText":"Architectural drawings","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Are there architectural drawings for your project?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":1498,"questionDisplayText":"Wall Construction Type","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What type of wall construction are you using?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":7069,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wood frame","answerDisplayText":"Wood frame","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3811,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Metal frame","answerDisplayText":"Metal frame","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3757,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Masonry","answerDisplayText":"Masonry","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":18055,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Framing not involved in project","answerDisplayText":"Framing not involved in project","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":7069,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Wood frame","answerDisplayText":"Wood frame","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3811,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Metal frame","answerDisplayText":"Metal frame","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3757,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Masonry","answerDisplayText":"Masonry","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1989,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Don't Know","answerDisplayText":"Don't Know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":18055,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Framing not involved in project","answerDisplayText":"Framing not involved in project","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/40032/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40032,"taskName":"Engineer - Structural","taskDescription":"Analyze a Structural Issue (Structural Engineer)","xmTaskDescriptor":"Structural Engineers","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":74,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"analyze engineer architecture engineer structural","textMessagingName":"Structural Engineer","rolloverLongDesc":"Includes examination \u0026 analysis of current structures to assess problems \u0026 solutions relating to collapse, cracking, detachment, sagging, etc.  Also includes analysis of proposed structures to make sure the design is adequate to prevent such problems.","rolloverShortDesc":"Credentialed structural engineer to review situation.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Analyze a Structural Issue (Structural Engineer).  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"\u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e Structural Engineers \u0026 Engineering Firms","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":5,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Structural Engineer","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Engineer - Structural","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Structural Engineer Need","urlName":"Engineer-Structural","taskConsiderationId":3,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Structural Engineers - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"analyze,engineer,architecture,engineer,structural,structure","emcCategoryOid":-12005,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":356,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}